我不要求任何東西
除許可外。
還有60名男子。我會選擇的男人
根據我自己的標準。
如果你決定加入他們,我會
也加入 SAS。
最親愛的米倫,你知道我愛你。
我知道我可以讓你這麼開心。
如果你出門,
這將是自殺。
誰？麥戈尼格爾,先生。
斯特林是怎麼回事
你這麼不喜歡？
我發明瞭SAS。
他無權毀滅
它執行了第一次任務。
我們還有第二次機會。
讓我們看看星星是什麼
為我們準備了。
槍雞巴
機槍射擊
那是帕迪·梅恩...
我在黑暗中
和沉默...
這不是比賽,先生。
當然是。
哦,我明白。
讓遊戲開始吧。
音樂:遊戲
作者:摩托黑德
狂笑
來吧,抓住他。
你覺得這些怎麼樣？
你到底從哪裡學的
像那樣開車,帕迪梅恩？
現在,我們將分成四個
單位和以前一樣。
我猜是同一個團隊
就像我們上次攻擊一樣
這些相同的簡易機場,只是為了保持
評分系統公平？
不。
不同的團隊,相同的團隊領導者。
因為這整個練習,
整個北非戰役
是關於我的團隊與你的團隊,
水稻。
贊成。
只要清楚就行。
先生們,這是一個劇院
戰爭,不是遊樂場。
而這次會有所不同,
因為現在德國人
都在期待我們。
每個簡易機場都將處於高位
警報。
更有趣,喬克。
所以現在也許是雙點
每摧毀一架飛機？
劉易斯,你會拿杏仁
和萊利到諾菲利亞簡易機場。
弗雷澤。。。我不要
參與這個愚蠢的遊戲。
..你會和路易斯一起去,
但是帶四個人休息
在簡易機場進行攻擊
西邊的機場。
而帕迪,就像上次一樣,
你會帶走塔梅特,我會帶走
蘇爾特。
那麼第二回合,先生。
哦,是的,第二輪。
那麼,先生,我可以加入您的團隊嗎？
當然可以,親愛的,
你堅持和帕迪叔叔在一起。
哦,她是一隻敏銳的小貓。
她是。
誰破壞最多
今晚的飛機將贏得一瓶
20 年單一麥芽威士卡
蘇格蘭威士卡！
歡呼
哦,我父親的最愛。
現在,我隨身攜帶以防萬一
我受了致命傷。
現在,我把它作為獎品提供
在我們的遊戲中。
帕迪,你有很多
你那個時代的威士卡。
沒有什麼比這更好的了,
考慮到你卑微的背景。
我能站在你們兩個之間嗎
他媽的
像校長這樣的白癡？
我自己,我更喜歡鍋,蒸餾
在浴缸裡。
但我很樂意接受這個
當我贏了,先生,請你動手。
好吧,夥計們,檢查一下你們的武器。
噴槍上膛
大衛。
這是什麼愚蠢的廢話
關於遊戲？
沒有指揮官曾經
能夠控制帕迪·梅恩
因為他們都不理解他。
他會和我爭戰
無論發生什麼。
但現在,他會努力留住
通過消滅敵人來佔據主導地位
飛機,這是必不可少的
如果我們不想讓托布魯克倒下。
是的,但它真的很聰明嗎
戰略,大衛,還是做
你只是想贏得比賽？
現在 幾點鐘？十分鐘到
午夜。
我們需要等待月亮落山。
讓我們在這裡等待月亮落山。
四英里到簡易機場。這
海岸路是
就在那個山脊上。
我們不能拿車輛冒險
任何進一步。
去他媽的月亮。
你來了,先生。
我們走吧。
遠方的聲音
厚顏無恥的混蛋已經忍受了
圍欄。
哎呀,厚臉皮的狐狸。
但它會讓它更有趣
這一次。
我認為我們應該等待月亮
解決 - 他們會看到我們。
不,月亮是我們的朋友。
耐心是我們的敵人。
此外,
那些看到我們的人很快就會死去。
聽。。。
低沉的隆隆聲
正如我想的那樣,柵欄
這次還有探照燈。
好吧。
我希望你讀這個。
在。。。
..我不信教,先生。
如果您無法閱讀列印件,
光線將足夠
對我們移動不利。
遞給我,這是我的最愛。
而且,呃,你在做什麼,先生？
我們至少還有15分鐘。
所以你讀你的聖經。
我要以我自己的方式祈禱。
低低的輕笑
我最親愛的米倫,
我發送已經兩周了
你我的求婚信。
我在想像我沒有
收到回復
由於郵件中的故障
服務。
我們現在以火星為基地。
郵件每藍月亮來一次。
說到月亮,每次
我看著它,我想起你。
太老套了,不是嗎？喜歡一個
那些糟糕的好萊塢電影。
她笑了
但月亮給了我希望
那東西如此寒冷和遙遠
可以顯得美麗。
我相信我也被認為是冷的
和一些人的遠端,我希望
你也可以考慮
我,如果不是美麗的,
那麼至少是可靠的。
我希望你的回答
我的建議將是肯定的。
光剛死
“你不要殺人”,先生。
好吧,我可以告訴你完整的
誡命 - 你不可殺人,
除非在一個很好的事業中。
每天,希特勒都派無辜者
到死為止。
所以我們有一個很好的理由。
弗雷澤。
帶你的人向西走。
我們向東走。
走得好,先生。
祝你好運,男孩們。
發動機修訂版
麥克,麥克...
德軍增援部隊正朝著
加入隆美爾。
我們無法到達蘇爾特簡易機場
沒有穿過那條路。
他媽的！
畫刀
德國之聲
公雞槍
悶悶的尖叫聲
刀斬
只有五個梅塞施密特在
帶。什麼意思？
五就是五。
五個梅塞施密特被取出
行動
挽救了英國人的生命。
狗屎
是的,先生。
我只希望有更多。
他們不在乎分數
黑板,我們誰都沒有。
好。
只有怪物會計數。
如果這是隆美爾的主要解脫
列,會有
三人間歇
小時。會有休息時間。
德軍緊緊逼
防止。。。會有血腥的
休息,薩德勒！
我會休息一下。
我他媽的欠休息一下！
音樂:生來就輸,
作者:約翰尼·雷霆
# 哦,事情就是這樣
# 城市太冷了
# 生來就要輸
# 寶貝我生來就要失去...#
狗屎
守衛喊叫
壞狗。
看起來帕迪點燃了另一個
篝火。
那麼,現在。他他媽的有什麼
炸了？
不管是什麼,我想有
對目的地幾乎沒有疑問
我父親最喜歡的威士卡。
笑聲
我父親會非常自豪。
就是這樣,道路暢通無阻。
這是最後一個。
現在 幾點鐘？
4:26 4:40 太陽升起。這是另一個
20分鐘行軍到蘇爾特簡易機場。
歎息:太晚了。
遙遠的轟隆隆
看起來像路易斯和弗雷澤
也取得了一些成功。
勇敢！
答案是肯定的。
道路變得清晰起來
當已經太晚了。
或者想像一個更有趣的
可能性。
道路變得清晰起來
因為為時已晚。
這其中蘊藏著一個至關重要的哲學
分別。
荷馬在《伊利亞特》中寫道:
命運與我們同生。
沒有人能逃脫它,也沒有
勇敢的人也不是懦夫。
你說什麼,薩德勒？
當他說話時,我說不
勇敢或怯懦。
事實上。
根本沒有人在說話。
何屁
如果你看到一塊棕色的石頭,羅格,
遠離它。
斯特林！
我們做到了。
我想寫下分數。
你為什麼不不管它,帕迪？
拜託,24加27...
50...
..1.
嚇跑傑裡斯,那個。
即使他們拿了額外的
注意事項,我認為
我們做得很好。
電線,狗,睜大眼睛,
儘管男孩。
是什麼導致了所有的煙花？
5,000加侖航空燃料。
啊。
我在我的統計中沒有算在內。
你呢？
誰會得到威士卡？
獎品不見了,帕迪。
有些我喝了,其餘的
被打成碎片。
決定這是一個毫無價值的姿態。
我的策略是醜陋而徒勞的,
一瓶威士卡不是
合適的獎勵
為了足智多謀和勇氣
你已經展示了兩個以上
非常危險的任務。
所以。。。
..我要推薦給GHQ
你被授予
傑出服務勳章
獎章和你得到晉陞
到上尉軍銜。
恭喜你,梅恩船長。
特種航空服務第一
戰鬥勳章和首次晉陞。
為帕迪船長歡呼三聲
梅恩,塔梅特的瘋狂混蛋
帶！
嘻嘻...
萬歲！
嘻嘻...萬歲！
現在你可以嘗試穿披風了
你自己的力量,
你這個叛變的愛爾蘭屄。
你看你...
你是第一任指揮官
我曾經真正喜歡過。
哼。
劉易斯到底在哪裡？
米倫？
她輕笑
你在幹什麼？
我在問我親愛的逝者
祖母問。
什麼問題？
你很神秘。
我們要去哪？
我祖母說是的。
所以讓我們去做吧。
在車後座！
這是所有年輕人
顯然,在美國是這樣。
呃......
她咯咯地笑
記住,你必須退出。
我會的,我的愛人。
我會的。
兩人都呻吟
我愛你,米倫。
呻吟
哦！
哦,哦,主啊！
什麼？
很快,看在上帝的份上。
我們該怎麼辦？
喜歡這個？是的,更快。
哦！
哦！善良。
這麼多！
他清了清嗓子
哦！
什麼？現在你毀了？
我的衣服被毀了。
嗯,米倫...
當我們結婚時,那裡
將不需要
用於戰略撤退。
你總是訴諸軍事術語
當你感到尷尬時。
你聽到我說話了嗎？
我說,當我們結婚的時候。
哦,喬克...
敵機,正南！
飛機無人機
大家,扇出去。小心！
杏仁,前往岩石。
大家都出去了。扇出！
拿起你的武器,掩護。
拿布倫槍。
散射！
大家散開！
下來吧,先生,還有另一個
飛機！顯然是自己做的
優先事項,如何
奉承。
杏仁,掩護。加油。
滾開！
他嘟囔著
喊
你被擊中了嗎,先生？
他們正在向後擺動。
鴨！你還好嗎,先生？
只是前往岩石。
我會在那裡見到你。
先生,你必須跑,跑。
跑？步行將是一件好事。
先生！你沒事吧？
呻吟
呼嚕 聲
喊叫,槍聲
先生！
您需要説明嗎？
呻吟
我們會來接你的。
回到岩石後面！
他們又來了！
呼嚕 聲
鳥兒鳴叫
運動員。
為了回答你的提議,我的
愛。。。
..我真的不得不說不。
我怎麼能嫁給一個男人
已經死了？
他嘟囔著
不。
不不不
不,米倫。
不。
不,我沒死。
我還活著。米倫...
我沒死,米倫！
我一會兒就和你在一起。
我盡可能快。
運動員！先生,你受傷了。
我來找你。
不要去那裡,那是
他媽的命令。我不會讓你
這。
喊
先生,我來了。
快到了,親愛的。
飛機無人機
炮火
只有一輛車。
我想知道德國人是否
有一塊黑板。
大家沒事吧,小夥子們？
你們沒事吧,夥計們？
給他們喝一杯。
喬克沒有成功。
什麼意思？
你是什麼意思？
你覺得我是什麼意思？
不。他在哪？
他他媽的死了。
嘿 嘿。。
他在哪？！
他就是他跌倒的地方。
你離開了他？
我離開了他...！
這就是他媽的協定！
你,按照你他媽的命令。
不要試圖檢索
墮落者的屍體
“因為它會阻礙迅速執行
給定任務“,先生。
他是一個血腥的爛攤子,在陽光下。
這就是我們在哪裡
現在都會
傑瑞在我們身上。
斯特林葛籣茨
我其實不相信
約翰·路易斯是人。
先生,熄滅你的香煙。
滾開！
他死得很好。
沙子,沙子,快。
所以。。。
..只有夢想家
瘋子離開了。
他媽的會是誰
現在明智的人？
親愛的喬克,我收到了你的信
今天早上,我跳了舞。
我居然和信一起跳舞
在我的手裡,好像是
你我和你一起跳舞。
我當然會嫁給你,喬克。
我當然會。
遊行。
注意力。
早上,先生們。
所有人:早上,先生。
他說:「早上好,先生們。
早上好,先生！
就像他媽的小學一樣。
放鬆。
好吧,如果這是小學,
我有消息
來自校長,
奧金萊克將軍本人。
但在我告訴之前
你他要說什麼...
..哀悼期
因為喬克·路易斯中尉結束了。
庫 珀
升旗。先生！
奧金萊克表示他的
對成功的驚訝
我們在這樣的成就
時間很短。
摧毀了90架敵機
三周后,
我們已經超過了這個數位
被英國皇家空軍摧毀
三倍。他媽的！
帕迪·梅恩的DSO一直是
確認並已晉陞
到上尉軍銜。先生？
它不起作用。
對,尋求,
現在説明那個可憐的孩子。
他媽的很高興,先生。
輝盛榮獲獎項
軍事十字勳章。
繩子被鉤住了,是嗎？
是的。
我已經晉陞為軍銜
的專業。
我們做了...我認為
是輪子。是他媽的
繩子,你嘖嘖。
嘿,這樣跟我說話,
我會把你的出血塊打掉！
那麼,繼續！他媽的清酒！
從大局來看,
逆境而上,我們現在
有主動權。
這種成功是沒有感謝的
你的工作一小部分,
SAS的人已經執行了。
我們之所以取得成功,是因為我們做到了
事情不同。
我們以自己的方式實現我們的目標。
去他媽的輪子。
去他媽的繩索。
就把他媽的東西綁起來。
表彰你的驚奇
成功,GHQ
五天都獎勵了你
離開。
我們可能不是正式團,
但是當你走自己的路時
到你在開羅的酒吧和妓院,
你們都會穿一個
其中 - 鮑勃·泰特的帽子徽章。
火焰之劍是傳說中的
劍神劍。
新的跳躍翅膀。
它們是由喬克設計的。
你們這些能讀書的人,
將閱讀座右銘
在我們的徽章上。
現在,帕迪,既然你已經體現了
最好的話,我會離開
給你說。
新的座右銘
的特別航空服務是 -
喝朗姆酒,打臟,操
規則。
新的座右銘是「誰敢贏」。
誰敢...贏了。
我們將繼續敢於。
有卡車
在帶你們去開羅的路上。
將貝雷帽戴在頭上,
和你巨大的雞巴上的避孕套。
僅此而已。
叛變的愛爾蘭屄請求
允許不前往開羅,
先生。
音樂:祝福他們所有人
作者:喬治·福姆比
嘿,小夥子們,誰
點了咖啡
這裡的霜淇淋蛋筒呢？
那麼什麼是白色引擎蓋
那麼,代表女士們嗎？
你是女童子軍嗎？
讓我看看。
哦,哦！不應該那樣做。
你覺得怎麼樣？
你們可愛的女士們想要哪一個
帶我去阿斯科特,過女士節？
什麼？記住,大衛男孩...
..即使我們無法理解
一個他媽的詞這些蘇格蘭浪蕩子
說。。。
..他們是英國人,而我們不是
允許殺死他們。
浪漫的音樂播放
鳥鳴
看在你媽的份上。
我受不了了
東西。。。抱怨。
滾開！
耶穌。
對不起。
你在開玩笑。
這他媽是怎麼回事,雷格？
..在我們的貝雷帽的顏色上！
其他人對我們有意見
他媽的頭飾？！
請向前走。
議員們來了！
雖然,我不得不說,關於
新貝雷帽的顏色,
他們確實有道理。
我聽說你的新支隊在做什麼
很好。
這不是我的超脫。
這是喬克的超脫。
我想現在是
我的,屬於我和那個瘋子。
這裡。謝謝。
如果你不喜歡金絲雀
在籠子里,你為什麼會得到一個？
的。。。所以我可以釋放它。
你可能認為我很富有同情心。
你沒有同情心嗎？
不,我不認為我是。
為了你的勝利。啊。。。
雖然你看起來像一個
失去。
是的,我是一個玩遊戲的男孩
而我父親看著...
..像往常一樣。
如果我沒有獲得最多的嘗試,
或跑得最多,
他不會和我說話
回家的路。
這是汽車的聲音
發動機、擋風玻璃雨刷器
和雷鳴般的咆哮
他的沉默。
我們出去喝一杯吧。
急什麼？
不著急。
只想看日落
從帝國俱樂部的陽臺上。
我寧願留在這裡。
還行。
真相。
有我要你去的人
遇。。。今晚。
絕密。
有我在想
你和我在一起
因為你喜歡我。
我非常努力地只喜歡
你。
什麼。
歐文！
歐文？！
你的身體
我想,在這裡遇見你的靈魂。
我要讀你,
荷馬或濟慈...
..但後來我想,去他媽的。
我想我曾經讓你厭煩過。
而你只是在禮貌。
你還記得那個愚蠢的珀西
我們以前唱的法語歌？
我會給你唱珀西法國的東西
我們會笑一笑。
# 我們會越過溝渠,我們的領導者
說著就把敵人從側翼拿下
# 但當時驚愕地大喊大叫
從各個等級中產生
# 用於張貼在高高的樹上
# 我們非常清楚地看到
# 非法侵入者被起訴
依法
# 我們被挫敗了,大膽地驚呼
斯萊特裡
# 我們的盛大活動到此結束
# 快樂地拋棄生命
面對那匹母馬和排水
# 現在我不像獅子那麼勇敢
但我比母雞勇敢
# 而打架逃跑的人
將活著再次戰鬥...#
哦,逃跑,嗯,歐文？
哦,多麼偉大的生活
那將是一個懦夫。
如此熱愛生活。
我想,我們今晚就睡在這裡。
親愛的上帝,我希望這不是
你的小驚喜。
看。。。
不,不是。
他見過我們。他喝醉了。
斯特林。斯特林少校,現在,我
聽見。
雖然我相信你個人
一無所獲。
我有東西給你。
看來我的幻影團
有了新的精神。
誰敢贏？
你他媽的從哪裡弄來的？
有人從酒吧里撿到的
鬥毆后的地板？
我的好朋友,人民委員部
開羅員警,告訴我
結果有七場戰鬥
受傷過紅燈
開羅區自10:00起
今天上午,其中六次涉及
戴著SAS貝雷帽的男人。
是的,他們是不會退縮的男人
如果他們受到侮辱,就下來。
哦,我明白。
以及顏色的選擇
是故意的。
克拉克先生,夏娃和我正在計劃
吃晚飯。
你選擇白色來挑釁
對質。
你看,親愛的,有
沒有什麼比酒吧鬥毆更像了
將男人聚集在一起。
有利於公司士氣。
克拉克先生,我在問
你禮貌地。
別管我們。
你是一個標本。
你一事無成。
然而你有膽量
重新設計我團的跳躍翅膀。
感謝您帶來SAS
成存在。
感謝您歸還貝雷帽。
現在,滾蛋。
你最好讓她教你
一些法國人,老男孩。
法國人正在向你走來,
他們是真正的交易。
他是什麼意思 - 法語
來找我？
讓我們跳舞吧。
好吧。
這他媽的到底是怎麼回事？
奧金萊克...
..他剛到。
常規。曼蘇爾小姐。
你好？斯特林。
一點兒。井
對於商業,
我更喜歡用英語。常規
奧金萊克,你怎麼來了？
好吧,您的成功給我們帶來了
在這裡,還有伯格船長的
請求説明。
請允許我。
我不要任何人
強加給我,
因此,我不要
強加給你。
強加什麼？
我有20個
最堅韌,最優秀的傘兵
在法國軍隊中,
在我的指揮下。
他們就像拴著皮帶的野狗,
想殺死德國人。
好吧,我們要部署
他們在沙漠中,
但他們必須接受培訓。
我們的首席培訓官
在行動中陣亡。
我們會找別人的。
一切都安排好了。
我們正在派遣法國傘兵
加入你。
由誰決定？
這是我的想法。
在那之前的一切
一直是該戰略的一部分。
我的首要任務是執行
的戰爭。
你的也是。
首先,你只會
必須饒恕一個人。有人
留下來訓練自由人
沙漠戰爭中的法國人。
但為了對付我的野性
狗,他必須是
一個非常堅強的人。
此部署何時開始？
好人。
來吧,喝一杯。
我們可以買幾把椅子嗎？
曼蘇爾小姐,你一定要告訴我
關於你最後幾天的一切...
鋼琴演奏
你找到他了嗎？
是的。
水稻。。。
..GHQ正在向我們派遣一支支隊
法國傘兵。
我們不需要更多的男人。
嗯,這是直接訂單
來自奧金萊克本人,一個恩惠
給戴高樂,承諾
由溫斯頓邱吉爾。
但我們需要有人
來訓練他們。
有經驗的人。
有人建立訓練營。
訓練他們在這個烤箱裡戰鬥
由沙子製成,你看。
誰？
井。。。
..隨著喬克的消失...
..沒有其他人經驗豐富
足夠或足夠堅韌。
我決定必須是你。
所以我留在賈洛,而你繼續
外出執行任務？
是的,當然,我們會
繼續我們的活動。
所以失敗者找到了獲勝的方法。
你知道,我的老爸,愛爾蘭人
從雙方,從雙方刺傷
像你這樣的男人。
蘭丹寧紳士。
帕迪,沒有其他人了。
他對我說生活
作為一個普通人,
他說。。。
你配不上我父親的
智慧。
右。好吧,聽著,帕迪。
哦 - 有時
當你在指揮時,
你需要製造困難
決定。
不彈他媽的鋼琴就走
在沙漠中觀光。
槍聲
我們完蛋了。
I'm not asking for anything
other than permission.
And 60 men. Men I will choose
according to my own criteria.
If you decide to join them, I will
join the SAS too.
Dearest Mirren, you know I love you.
I know I could make you so happy.
If you go out in this,
it will be suicide.
Who? McGonigal, sir.
What is it about Stirling
that you dislike so much?
I invented the SAS.
He had no right to destroy
it on its first mission.
We have a second chance.
Let's see what the stars
have in store for us.
GUNS COCK
MACHINE GUN FIRE
That's Paddy Mayne...
And here am I in the dark
and silent...
It's not a competition, sir.
Of course it is.
Oh, I see.
Let the games begin.
MUSIC: The Game
by Motorhead
LAUGHS WILDLY
Come on, catch him.
How do you like these?
Where the hell did you learn
to drive like that, Paddy Mayne?
Now, we will break off into four
units as before.
I'm guessing it's the same teams
as the last time we attacked
these same airstrips, just to keep
the scoring system fair?
Nope.
Different teams, same team leaders.
Because this whole exercise,
the whole North Africa campaign
is about my team versus your team,
Paddy.
Aye.
Just as long as that is clear.
Gentlemen, this is a theatre
of war, not a playground.
And this time it will be different,
because now the Germans
are expecting us.
Every airstrip will be on high
alert.
Even more fun, Jock.
So now perhaps double points
for each plane destroyed?
Lewes, you will take Almonds
and Riley to Nofilia airstrip.
Fraser... I want no
part in this idiotic game.
..you will go with Lewes,
but take four men and break
off at the airstrip to attack
the airfield to the west.
And Paddy, just as the last time,
you will take Tamet and I will take
Sirte.
Round two then, sir.
Oh, yes, round two.
Can I come on your team, then, sir?
Of course you can, sweetheart,
you stick with Uncle Paddy.
Oh, she's a keen kitten.
She is.
And whoever destroys the most
aeroplanes tonight will win a bottle
of 20-year-old single malt
Scotch whisky!
CHEERING
Oh, my father's favourite.
Now, I carry it with me in case
I'm fatally wounded.
Now, I'm offering it as a prize
in our game.
Paddy, you've had a lot
of whisky in your time.
Nothing as good as this,
considering your humble background.
Shall I stand between you two
fucking
idiots like a headmaster?
Myself, I prefer potcheen, distilled
in bathtubs.
But I will gladly take this
pish off your hands when I win, sir.
OK, men, check your weapons.
GUNS COCKING
David.
What's this idiotic nonsense
about a game?
No commanding officer has ever
been able to control Paddy Mayne
because none of them understood him.
He will fight against me
come what may.
But now, he will try to retain
dominance by destroying enemy
aircraft, which is essential
if we don't want Tobruk to fall.
Yes, but is it really clever
strategy, David, or do
you just want to win the game?
What time is it? Ten minutes to
midnight.
We need to wait for the moon to set.
Let's wait here for the moon to set.
Four miles to the airstrip. The
coast road is
just over that ridge.
We can't risk the vehicles
any further.
Fuck the moon.
There you are, sir.
Let's go.
VOICES IN DISTANCE
The cheeky bastards have put up
fences.
Aye, cheeky fox.
But it'll make it more fun
this time.
I think we should wait for the moon
to settle - they'll see us.
No, the moon is our friend.
Patience is our enemy.
And besides,
those that see us will soon be dead.
Listen...
DEEP RUMBLING
Just as I thought, fences
and searchlights this time.
All righty.
I want you to read this.
Um...
..I'm not religious, sir.
If you're unable to read the print,
the light will be sufficiently
bad for us to move.
Pass it me, it's my favourite.
And, er, what are you doing, sir?
We have at least 15 more minutes.
So you read your Bible.
I'm going to pray in my own way.
LOW CHUCKLE
My dearest Mirren,
it has been two weeks since I sent
you my letter of marriage proposal.
I'm imagining that I haven't
received a response
because of faults in the mail
service.
We are now based on the planet Mars.
And mail comes once every blue moon.
And speaking of the moon, every time
I look at it, I think of you.
So damn corny, isn't it? Like one
of those awful Hollywood films.
SHE LAUGHS
But the moon gives me hope
that something so cold and remote
can appear beautiful.
I believe I too am considered cold
and remote by some, and I am hoping
that you might also consider
me, if not beautiful,
then at least dependable.
And I hope that your answer
to my proposal will be yes.
The light died just after
"Thou shalt not kill", sir.
Well, I can tell you the full
commandment - Thou shalt not kill,
except in a very good cause.
Every day, Hitler sends innocents
to their deaths.
So we have a very good cause.
Fraser.
Take your men west.
We go east.
Go well, sir.
Best of luck, boys.
ENGINES REV
Mac, Mac...
German reinforcements heading
to join Rommel.
We can't reach Sirte airstrip
without crossing that road.
Fuck!
DRAWS KNIFE
GERMAN VOICES
COCKS GUN
MUFFLED SCREAM
KNIFE SLASHES
Only five Messerschmitts on the
strip. Meaning what?
Five is five.
Five Messerschmitts taken out of
action,
British lives saved.
DOG BARKS
Yes, sir.
I only wish there were more.
They don't care about the scores on
the blackboard, none of us do.
Good.
Only monsters would keep count.
If that's Rommel's main relief
column, there will be
no break for three
hours. There will be a break.
German troops stay tight to
prevent... There will be a bloody
break, Sadler!
I will get a break.
I am owed a fucking break!
MUSIC: Born to Lose,
by Johnny Thunders
# Oh, that's the way it goes
# The city is so cold
# Born to lose
# Baby I'm born to lose... #
DOG BARKS
GUARD SHOUTS
Bad dog.
Looks like Paddy's lit another
bonfire.
Now, then. what the fuck has he
blown up?
Whatever it is, I imagine there's
little doubt about the destination
of my father's favourite whisky.
LAUGHTER
My father would be very proud.
That's it, road's clear.
That's the last of them.
What time is it?
4:26 sun rises at 4:40. It's another
20-minute march to Sirte airstrip.
SIGHS: It's too late.
DISTANT BOOMING
Looks like Lewes and Fraser
have had some success, too.
Bravo!
Of course.
The road became clear
when it was already too late.
Or imagine a more amusing
possibility.
The road became clear
BECAUSE it was too late.
Therein lies a crucial philosophical
distinction.
In The Iliad, Homer wrote,
Fate is born with us.
No man escapes it, neither
brave man nor coward.
What do you say, Sadler?
I say no when he's talking
of bravery or cowardice.
Indeed.
No-one is talking at all.
HE FARTS
If you see a brown stone, Rog,
stay away from it.
Stirling!
We done it.
I want to write down the scores.
Why don't you leave it alone, Paddy?
Rog, 24 plus 27...
50...
..1.
Scare the Jerries off, that.
Even though they took extra
precautions, I think
we did rather well.
Wires, dogs, wide-eyed,
boys notwithstanding.
What caused all the fireworks?
5,000 gallons of aviation fuel.
Ah.
I'm not counting that in my tally.
What about you?
Who's getting the whisky?
The prize has gone, Paddy.
Some of it I drank, the rest
shot to pieces.
Decided it was a worthless gesture.
My strategy was ugly and vain,
and a bottle of whisky is not
a fitting reward
for the resourcefulness and courage
you have shown over two
very dangerous assignments.
So...
..I'm going to recommend to GHQ
that you be awarded
the Distinguished Service Order
Medal and that you be promoted
to the rank of captain.
Congratulations, Captain Mayne.
The Special Air Services first
combat medal and first promotion.
Three cheers for Captain Paddy
Mayne, the mad bastard of Tamet
strip!
Hip-hip...
Hooray!
Hip-hip... Hooray!
Now you can try wearing the mantle
of power yourself,
you mutinous Irish cunt.
You see you...
You are the first commanding officer
that I've ever actually liked.
Huh.
Where in the hell is Lewes?
Mirren?
SHE CHUCKLES
What are you doing?
I was asking my dear-departed
grandmother a question.
What question?
You're being very mysterious.
Where are we going?
My grandmother said yes.
So let's do it.
In the back of the car!
It's what all the young people
in America do, apparently.
Erm...
SHE GIGGLES
Remember, you have to pull out.
I will, my love.
I will.
BOTH GROAN
I love you, Mirren.
GROANING
Oh!
Oh, oh, Lord!
What?
Quickly, for God's sake.
What do we do?
Like this? Yes, quicker.
Oh!
Oh! Goodness.
Such a lot!
HE CLEARS THROAT
Oh!
What? Now you are ruined?
My dress is ruined.
Well, Mirren...
When we're married, there
will be no need
for strategic withdrawals.
You always resort to military terms
when you're embarrassed.
Did you hear me?
I said, when we're married.
Oh, Jock...
Enemy aircraft, due south!
AIRCRAFT DRONE
Everyone, fan out. Watch out!
Almonds, head for the rocks.
Everyone out. Fan out!
Grab your weapons, take cover.
Get the Bren gun.
Scatter!
Everybody scatter!
Get down, sir, there's another
plane! Obviously made ourselves
something of a priority, how
flattering.
Almonds, take cover. Come on.
Fuck off!
HE GRUNTS
SHOUTING
Are you hit, sir?
They're swinging back 'round.
Duck! Are you OK, sir?
Just head for the rocks.
I'll meet you there.
Sir, you have to run, run.
Run? Walk would be a fine thing.
Sir! Are you OK?
GROANS
GRUNTS
SHOUTING, GUNFIRE
Sir!
Do you need help?
GROANS
We'll come and get you.
Get back behind the rocks!
They're coming again!
GRUNTS
BIRDS CHIRP
Jock.
In answer to your proposal, my
love...
..I really have to say no.
How can I marry a man who's
already dead?
HE GRUNTS
No.
No, no, no.
No, Mirren.
No.
No, I'm not dead.
I'm alive. Mirren...
I'm not dead, Mirren!
I'll be with you in a moment.
As quickly as I can.
Jock! Sir, you're hurt.
I'll come to you.
Do not go down there, that's a
fucking order. I will not let you
die.
SHOUTING
Sir, I'm coming.
Almost there, darling.
AIRCRAFT DRONES
GUNFIRE
There's only one vehicle.
I wonder if the Germans
have a blackboard.
Everyone all right, lads?
You all right, fellas?
Get them a drink.
Jock didn't make it.
What-what do you mean?
What do you mean?
What do you think I mean?
No. Where is he?
He's fucking dead.
Hey, hey..
Where is he?!
He's where he fell.
You left him?
I left him...!
That's the fucking protocol!
You, on your fucking order.
"Do not attempt to retrieve
the bodies of the fallen
"as it will impede swift execution
of the given mission", sir.
He's a bloody mess, out in the sun.
Which is where we
are all going to be, now
that Jerry is onto us.
STIRLING GRUNTS
I actually didn't believe
John Lewes was human.
Sir, put out your cigarette.
Fuck off!
He died well.
Sand, sand, quick.
So...
..only the dreamer
and the madman left.
Who the fuck is going to be
the sensible one now?
Dear Jock, I received your letter
this morning, and I danced.
I actually danced with the letter
in my hand as if it was
you I was dancing with.
Of course I will marry you, Jock.
Of course I will.
Parade.
Attention.
Morning, gentlemen.
ALL: Morning, sir.
He said, "Good morning, gentlemen."
GOOD MORNING, SIR!
Like fucking primary school.
Relax.
Well, if this is primary school,
I've had a message
from the headmaster,
General Auchinleck himself.
But before I tell
you what he has to say...
..the period of mourning
for Lieutenant Jock Lewes is over.
Cooper,
hoist the flag. Sir!
Auchinleck expresses his
astonishment at the success
that we have achieved in such
a short space of time.
Having destroyed 90 enemy aircraft
in three weeks,
we have exceeded the number
destroyed by the RAF
by a factor of three. Fuck!
Paddy Mayne's DSO has been
confirmed and he has been promoted
to the rank of captain. Sir?
It's not working.
Right, Seekings,
help that poor boy now.
Fucking gladly, sir.
Fraser has been awarded
the Military Cross.
Rope snagged, is it?
Yeah.
And I have been promoted to the rank
of major.
We have made... I think
it's the wheel. It's the fucking
rope, you oaf.
Hey, talk to me like that,
I'll knock your bleeding block off!
Go on, then! Fuck sake!
In the bigger picture,
against the odds, we now
have the initiative.
This success is in thanks in no
small part to the work that you,
the men of the SAS have carried out.
We achieve our success because we do
things differently.
We achieve our goals in our own way.
Fuck wheels.
Fuck ropes.
Just tie the fucking thing.
In recognition of your startling
successes, GHQ
have awarded you all five days
leave.
We may not be an official regiment,
but when you make your way
to your bars and brothels in Cairo,
you will all be wearing one
of these - cap badges by Bob Tait.
The flaming sword is the legendary
sword Excalibur.
New jump wings.
They were designed by Jock.
Those of you that can read,
will have read the motto
on our badge.
Now, Paddy, since you have embodied
the words best, I will leave
it to you to say them.
The new motto
of the Special Air Service is -
drink rum, fight dirty, fuck the
rules.
The new motto is Who Dares Wins.
Who dares...wins.
And we will continue to dare.
There are trucks
on the way to take you all to Cairo.
Wear the beret on your head,
and a condom on your massive cocks.
That'll be all.
Mutinous Irish cunt requesting
permission not to travel to Cairo,
sir.
MUSIC: Bless 'Em All
by George Formby
Hey, lads, who
ordered the coffee
and the ice cream cones here?
So what's the white bonnet
represent, then, ladies?
Are you Girl Scouts?
Let me see that.
Oh, oh! Shouldn't have done that.
What do you think?
Which one of you lovely ladies wants
to take me to Ascot, for Ladies Day?
What? Remember, Davey boy...
..even though we can't understand
a fucking word these Scotch wankers
say...
..they are British and we're not
allowed to kill them.
ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS
BIRD CHIRPS
For fuck's sake.
I can't bear this
thing...complaining.
Fuck off!
Jesus.
I'm sorry.
You're joking.
What the fuck's going on, Reg?
..Over the colour of our berets!
Anybody else have an opinion on our
fucking headgear?!
Please step forward.
MPs are coming!
Although, I have to say, regarding
the colour of the new beret,
they do have a point.
I hear your new detachment's doing
very well.
This isn't really my detachment.
It's Jock's detachment.
I suppose now it is
mine, belongs to me and that madman.
Here. Thank you.
If you don't like canaries
in cages, why did you get one?
Er...so I can set it free.
You might think I'm compassionate.
Are you not compassionate?
No, I don't think I am.
To your victories. Ah...
Though you look like someone who is
losing.
Yes, I am a boy playing a game
while my father watches...
..as he always did.
If I don't score the most tries,
or make the most runs,
he won't speak to me all
the way home.
It's the sound of the car
engine, the windscreen wipers
and the thunderous roar
of his silence.
Let's go out for a drink.
What's the rush?
No rush.
Just want to see the sunset
from the balcony of the Empire Club.
I would, er, rather stay here.
OK.
The truth.
There's someone I want you to
meet...tonight.
Top secret.
And there was me thinking
that you were with me
because you liked me.
I'm trying very hard to only like
you.
Come.
Owen!
Owen?!
Your bodies
meet your spirits here, I think.
I was going to read you,
Homer or Keats...
..but then I thought, fuck that.
I think I used to bore you with it.
And you were just being polite.
You remember that idiotic Percy
French song we used to sing?
I'll sing you the Percy French thing
and we'll have a laugh.
# We'll cross the ditch, our leader
said and take the foe in flank
# But yells of consternation then
arose from every rank
# For posted high upon a tree
# We very plainly saw
# Trespassers prosecuted in
accordance with the law
# We're foiled, exclaimed bold
Slattery
# Here ends our grand campaign
# Tis merrily throwing life away
to face that mare and drain
# Now I'm not as brave as lions
but I'm braver than the hen
# And he who fights and runs away
will live to fight again... #
Oh, to run away, eh, Owen?
Oh, how grand a life
it would be to be a coward.
To love life that much.
We'll sleep here tonight, I think.
Dear God, I do hope this isn't
your little surprise.
Look...
No, it isn't.
He's seen us. And he's drunk.
Stirling. Major Stirling, now, I
hear.
Although I believe you personally
have achieved nothing.
I have something for you.
It seems my phantom regiment
has a new ethos.
Who Dares Wins?
Where the fuck did you get that?
Someone picked it off a barroom
floor after a brawl?
My great friend, the Commissariat
of Cairo Police, tells me
there were seven fights resulting
in injury across the red light
district of Cairo since 10:00
this morning, six of them involving
men wearing the SAS beret.
Yes, they are men who will not back
down if they are insulted.
Oh, I see.
And the choice of colour
was deliberate.
Mr Clarke, Eve and I are planning
to have dinner.
You chose white to provoke
confrontation.
You see, my dear, there's
nothing like a barroom brawl
to bring men together.
Good for company morale.
Mr Clarke, I am asking
you politely.
Leave us alone.
You are a specimen.
You've achieved nothing.
Yet you have the audacity to
redesign my regiment's jump wings.
Thank you for bringing the SAS
into being.
Thank you for returning the beret.
Now, fuck off.
You'd better get her to teach you
some French, old boy.
The French are coming your way,
and they are the real deal.
What did he mean - French
coming my way?
Let's dance.
All right.
What the fuck is this all about?
Auchinleck...
..he just arrived.
General. Miss Mansour.
How do you do? Stirling.
A little. Well,
for business,
I prefer to use English. General
Auchinleck, what brings you here?
Well, your success brings us
here, and Captain Berge's
request for help.
Please, allow me.
I would not want anyone
to impose upon me,
therefore, I don't want
to impose on you.
Impose what?
I have 20 of
the toughest, finest paratroopers
in the French Army,
under my command.
They're like wild dogs on leashes,
wanting to kill Germans.
Well, we want to deploy
them in the desert,
but they have to be trained.
Our chief training officer
was killed in action.
We'll find somebody else.
It's all been arranged.
We're sending French paratroopers
to join you.
Decided by who?
This was my idea.
And everything up until then
has been part of the strategy.
My first priority is the execution
of the war.
So is yours.
To begin with, you'd only
have to spare one man. Somebody
left behind to train the Free
French in desert warfare.
But in order to deal with my wild
dogs, he would have to be
a very strong man.
When would this deployment begin?
Good man.
Come on, have a drink.
Can we get some chairs?
Miss Mansour, you must tell me
all about your last few days...
PIANO PLAYS
Did you find him?
Yep.
Paddy...
..GHQ are sending us a detachment
of French paratroopers.
We don't need many more men.
Well, it's a direct order
from Auchinleck himself, a favour
to Charles de Gaulle, promised
by Winston Churchill.
But we would need someone
to train them.
Someone with experience.
Someone to set up a training camp.
Train them to fight in this oven
made of sand, you see.
Who?
Well...
..with Jock gone...
..there is no-one else experienced
enough or tough enough.
I've decided it has to be you.
So I stay in Jalo while you continue
to go out on missions?
Yes, of course, we will
continue our campaign.
So the loser finds a way to win.
You know, my old dad, Irish
from both sides, stabbed from both
sides by men like you.
Landowning gentry.
Paddy, there is no-one else..
He said to me about life
as a common man,
he said...
You don't deserve my father's
wisdom.
Right. Well, listen, Paddy.
Oh - sometimes
when you are in command,
you need to make difficult
decisions.
Not play the fucking piano and go
sightseeing in the desert.
GUNSHOTS
We're fucked.